A.SANDRO JUDITH

M.B.A / B.E

+91 6384194317 ,9384411313

sandrojudith980@gmail.com

Mettutheru, Villivakkam, Chennai

PROFILE

I am an efficient and confident manager with demonstrated experience of working in the administrative and marketing Department. My experienced helped me develop expert knowledge of the sales process and supply chain. I am highly motivated to continue learning and improving my craft.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Development Manager

IGO Agri Tech farms Nov-2022 - Present

Administrative Manager

Vimanna labs india Pvt.Ltd (Agri.Drone sales & Service) April 2022- November

Administrative Manager

Aerial Drobotics Pvt. Ltd (Agri.Drone sales & Service) February 2021-March 2022

- ✓ Handling sales calls and business development, responsible for helping organizations obtain better brand recognition and financial growth.
- ✓ Coordinate with company executives and sales & marketing professionals to review current market trends in order to propose new business ideas that can improve revenue margins.
- ✓ Preparing quotations and invoice ,designing catalog price list based on customer requirement as well as company development
- ✓ Managing accounts and billing, invoice making works.

 Preparing documents and doing document related works and computer based works and drone assembly
- ✓ Designing catalog, price list, ad post like Facebook and Instagram etc.
- ✓ Responsible for all management activities, handling multi tasking in various department Versatile professional with excellent organizational skills. Capable of managing multiple task simultaneously and meeting tight timelines.
- ✓ Preparing billing and invoicing, sales budgets and projections.
- ✓ Manages inventory tracking system to record deliveries, shipments and stock level

EDUCATION

M.B.A Finance and Accounting

Madras university -Chennai -pursuing

B.E Agriculture (2016-2020)-86 %

Paavai Engineering College, Namakkal

Higher Secondary (2016)-80%

Dalmia higher Secondary school, Dalmia puram

SSLC (2014)-82%

Dalmia higher Secondary school, Dalmia puram

SKILLS

- * Account Management
- Staff handling and Management
- Microsoft Excel, word, power point
- Billing, invoicing and quotation Making
- Designing (Canva, Photoshop)
- Tally
- SAP (FICO)

AREA OF INTEREST

- Agriculture Farming
- Inventory Management
- Content development
- Farm mechanization

PROJECTS

- Solar-powered multi-purpose farming vehicle 2020
- * Effect of different casing in Milky mushroom production 2019
- * Solar powered integrated insect trapper-2019
- Dripso Aquaponics- 2018

CERTIFICATES

- Our project "Solar powered integrated insect trapper" to select one of the best projects from our department to submit to the event "Indo-Taiwan Submit".
- Complete one- day training program on **Mushroom Production** Technology at TNAU, Coimbatore
- Complete the industrial training at John deere Pvt. Ltd, attur.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name - M. Arockiya Raj

Date of Birth - 04-08-1998

Marital Status - Unmarried

Nationality - Indian
Gender - Female

- Tamil, English

Languages Known
- 4/51,South Street Vadugarpet,Trichy-621651

Native